your Russians, this Yeltsin and Gorbachev,
ваши вот русские этот Ельцинш и Горбачёв
yes, they took our 15 Slavic republics and
да взяли наших 15 славянских республик
stupidly broke them up into separate territories,
тупо развалили на отдельные территории
Gorbachev took them and withdrew troops from East
горбачёв взял вывел войска из Восточной
Germany and let them destroy that little
Германии дал им развалить эту стеночку
Berlin wall that our grandfathers built, and he withdrew
берлинскую которую наши деды строили да
troops from Eastern Europe, all
вывел войска из Восточной Европы все
these Czech Republics, Poland, Hungary, and the
эти Чехии Польши Венгрии там сразу
Americans immediately made color revolutions, all
американцы сделали цветные революции все
these Vaclavs, Havels, Lechs, Walentzes, and so it
эти вацлавы Гавелы Лехи Валенцы да вот и
turns out that when the Soviet
получается таким образом когда Советская
army left Eastern Europe,
армия ушла из Восточной Европы
naturally NATO moved, this holy
естественно НАТО подвинулась это свято
place is never empty,
место пусто не бывает
hello, hello, where are you from in
здравствуйте здравствуйте вы откуда в
Tagliata, it’s cool in honor of an Italian,
Тальяте прикольно в честь итальянца
and where are you from,
а вы откуда
from Samara, but I live in Ukraine,
из Самары родом но живу в Украине
yeah, and where are you broadcasting now, it seems to me,
угу а вы где сейчас вещаете мне кажется
which Switzerland, the city of Khmelnitsky, the city of
какой Швейцарии город Хмельницкий город
Khmelnitsky, it’s clear, Samara, I was born
Хмельницкий понятно прямо Самара родом
really when I was 3 years old, my parents, and what district,
реально в 3 года родители а какой район
what street, I have no idea, I was 3
какая улица понятия не имею мне было 3
years old when my parents came to Ukraine,
года когда родители приехали в Украину
it was still under the Soviet Union, they were sent
это ещё при Советском Союзе их направили
here to work at the factory in Kharkov and they
сюда на завод работать в Харьков и
stayed here, they are in Ukraine, well,  that is,
остались тут они в Украине а ну то есть
you have no Samara, that is, I
Самары у вас воспина никаких нет то есть
understand, none, yes,
Понял никаких да
what shall we discuss? I remember the swing only in
что обсудим я помню качельку только в
the yard, so vaguely, and that too, well, that's also a
дворе вот так смутно и то тоже ну тоже
good memory. The
хорошее воспоминание
question is: what do you think, why is
вопрос такой: как вы считаете зачем
Russia fighting not with the Anglo-Saxons, but with its
Россия воюет не с англосакцами а с
Slavic brothers? An
братьями славянами
interesting question, and
вопрос интересный а
firstly, we are fighting with the Anglo-Saxons, but
во-первых мы воем с англосаксами но
conditionally brothers who have ceased to be brothers to us,
братья условно которые нам братьями
even in my opinion, the
перестали быть даже по моему мнению
last one wanted to play this game with the
последнему захотели играть в эту
Anglo-Saxons, put themselves in a position
англосаксами поставить себя в ту позицию
where we play with a ball, and the ball is Ukraine, they
где мы играем мячом а мяч Украина они
wanted, they demanded, there
хотели они требовали это предупреждение
was a lot of warning, Minsk-1, Minsk 2, Istanbul
было много минск-1 Минск 2 Стамбульские
agreements, there was a lot of talk, stop it, but
соглашения говорок было много прекратите
let's stop and stop the
но давайте остановимся и прекратим
image, but no, Ukrainians are free, they are not
образи но нет украинцы вольные они не
brothers, in my opinion, they decided to us: "No, let's
братья по моему мнению нам решили: "Нет
fight." Well, you chose, we
давайте будем биться" ну вы выбрали мы
accepted your challenge, we are fighting, we are fighting with the
приняли ваш вызов бьёмся мы бьёмся и с
Anglo-Saxon world, and some part of
англосаксонским миром и некоторая часть
it has fallen away in the form of Trump, I'm tired, well, we need to
его отпала в виде Трампа устала ну надо
fight with China, and we need ammunition, and
воевать с Китаем и нужны боеприпасы а
here there is a huge shortage, and we need to pay
здесь прорва не хватает и нужно платить
salaries.  you need to pay
зарплату нужно платить
food, gasoline, ammunition, bullets,
питание бензин солдатам боеприпасы пули
cartridges, Ukraine produces
патроны украина же ничего не производит
absolutely nothing, nothing, not even to feed its own, it won’t be
абсолютно ничего даже кормить своих не
able to do so in terms of salaries, well, maybe there will be
сможет в плане зарплат ну может быть
food, of course, in this regard, the
корм найдётся конечно в этом плане
Anglo-Saxon world is already tired and we see the
англосакский мир уже устал и мы видим
results, well, the question is, look, the
результаты да ну вопрос смотрите
Anglo-Saxon strategy has always been to
стратегия англосакса всегда была
pit peoples against peoples, there, Slavs
стравливать народы с народами там славян
against Slavs, and so on, and it turns out
с славянами и так дальше и получается
that the Anglo-Saxons
что англосаксы
in 1991 destroyed the
в девяносто первом году развалили
Soviet Union, your Russians, this
Советский Союз ваши вот русский этот
Yeltsin and Gorbachev, yes, they took our 15
Ельцин и Горбачёв да взяли наших 15
Slavic republics, stupidly broke them up into
славянских республик тупо развалили на
separate territories, Gorbachev took and withdrew troops
отдельные территории горбачёв взял вывел
from East Germany, let them
войска из Восточной Германии дал им
destroy this little Berlin wall
развалить эту стеночку берлинскую
that our grandfathers built, yes, he withdrew
которую наши деды строили да вывел
troops from Eastern Europe, all
войска из Восточной Европы все
these Czech Republics, Poland, Hungary, the
эти Чехии Польши Венгрии там сразу
Americans immediately made color revolutions, all
американцы сделали цветные революции все
these Vaclavs, Havels, Lechs, Walentzes, yes, and so it
эти вацлавы Гавелы Лехи Валенцы да вот и
turns out that when the Soviet
получается таким образом когда Советская
army left Eastern Europe,
армия ушла из Восточной Европы
naturally NATO moved, this holy
естественно НАТО подвинулась это свято
place is never empty, yes, if the
место пусто не бывает да если там не
Soviet Union is not there, as
стоит Советский Союз как говорил ээ
Comrade Stalin said, yes, then there  there will be
товарищ Сталин да то там будут стоять
American soldiers and that's how it
американские солдаты и так оно
turned out and it turns out that in
получилось и выходит что в девяносто
1991 your Yeltsin and Gorbachev
первом году ваши Ельцин и Горбачёв
betrayed us all 15 Slavic republics
предали нас все 15 славянских республик
betrayed: Kazakhs Estonians Ukrainians
предали: казахов эстонцев украинцев
Russians Americans immediately approached the
русских американцы сразу подошли к
borders of Ukraine in Poland in Romania
границам Украины в Польше в Румынии
NATO bases in the Baltic countries
натовские базы в странах Балтии украину
took Ukraine into circulation and then took Russia into
взяли в оборот и Россию тогда взяли в
circulation you know yes under Yeltsin you had
оборот вы же знаете да при Ельцине у вас
Americans running everything, appointing
американцы рулили всем расставляли и
ministers and so on then you defaulted
министров и так дальше дефолт вам
and it turns out Ukraine was made
сделали и получается Украину поставили в
dependent the richest Ukraine
зависимость богатейшую Украину в
dependent on the United States of
зависимость от Соединённых Штатов
America from the Anglo-Saxons your Gorbachev and
Америки от англосаксов ваш Горбачёв и
Yeltsin simply gave into their hands take it
Ельцин просто отдали в руки забирайте
now instead of in short wait
теперь вместо того чтобы короче подожди
instead of taking and
вместо вместо того чтобы взять и сделать
striking Berlin like your grandfathers in 1945
удар по Берлину как деды в сорок пятом
yes you took and struck Bakhmut
да вы взяли сделали удар по Бахмуту
Mariupol Kharkov Kyiv against the Slavic
Мариуполю Харькову Киеву по славянскиму
people the question will sound because I'm bored
народу вопрос прозвучит а то мне скучно
yes the question is the question is why are you
да вопрос в том вопрос в том зачем вы
killing your Slavic brothers if you can
убиваете братьев славян если можно
kill your Anglo-Saxons
убивать англосаксов
historical excursion in my opinion
ваш исторический экскурс по моему мнению
basically at the beginning there
в основе своей в начале искажение
is a distortion from here you have a great
имеется отсюда у вас пошло великое
distortion the further the more difficult what
искажение чем дальше тем сложнее какое
distortion the Soviet Union I did not
искажение советский Союз я вас не
interrupt you that is why you spoke for a long time a couple of
перебивал поэтому вы долго говорили пару
minutes please do not interrupt me a-
минут меня пожалуйста не перебивайте
e look in my opinion it is in
а-э смотрите по моему мнению оно в
principle well most likely there is no general principle
принципе ну общей принципа скорее всего
but the Soviet Union which was ruled
нет но Советский Союз котором заруливали
absolutely in the majority at the final
абсолютно в большинстве на финальном
stage by Ukrainian leaders Brezhnev from
этапе украинские вожди Брежнев из
Dnepropetrovsk Khrushchev as it was this
Днепропетровска Хрущёв как был это
process
процесс
as if Slavic such and it was from the very
как бы славянский такой и он был самого
beginning was in a dead end branch of development there were
начально был в тупиковый ветразвития там
branches of communist rule which
ветв коммунистическое правление была
was it was a dead end it in the final
которая была она тупиковая она финальном
showed that it was a dead end and all this
показала что она тупиковая и вся эта
elite that ruled communist
элита которая рулила коммунистическая
it it was Ukrainian also ruled
она она украинская тоже так же рулила
it do not remove responsibility you in
она не снимайте ответственности вы в
some moments throw in that you
некоторых моментах накидываете что вы в
stood aside no you participated in this process
стороне стояли нет вы в этом процессе
this elite admitted that
участвовали эта элита призналась что на
just in case that it does not work out neither
всякий случай что не получается ни
jeans nor anything that to feed the whole world to
джинсов ничего что на весь мир накормить
arm socialist communism
вооружить социалистический коммунизма не
will not work but still everything close to the body
получится а всё-таки всё близкое к телу
native close  it is necessary to pass on mansions
родное близкое нужно передавать особняки
by inheritance it would be good to own
по наследству хорошо бы и владеть
communist enterprises and cars
коммунистическими предприятиями и машины
and drivers and the service staff that
и водители и ту обслугу которая уже у
they already had it would also be good to have just
них была тоже бы хорошо бы иметь просто
need to switch formation and they, so to
надо формацию перейти и они условно
speak, having agreed in the year in eighty-
говоря сговорившись в году в восемьдесят
one in eighty-nine in Talyat there was
первом году в восьмидесятом в Тальяте
sausage butter by coupon Gorbachev
была колбаса масла по талоном горбачёв
came a new one announced perestroika already in
пришёл новую объявил перестройку уже в
eighty-nine there was everything
восемьдесят девятом полону было всё
accordingly it reminded me as a
соответственно мне это напомнило как
well-known fact in 1917 in
общеизвестный факт в 1917 году в
St. Petersburg they made a revolution there was no
Санкт-Петербурге революцию произвели не
bread and the bread was held back so here
было хлеба а хлеб был придержали так вот
I roughly imagine when Gorbachev
я примерно представляю когда Горбачёв
came and here is this idea that the elites
пришёл и вот эту идею которую элиты в
had in their thoughts that is in every city in
мыслях носили то есть в каждом городе в
Talyat there is a sausage bread factory and
Тальяте есть колбас хлебный завод и
so on and every month and week they
прочее и каждую они месяц неделю
met the directors as communists in
встречались директора как коммунисты в
port meetings and there you could calmly
портсобраниях и там можно было спокойно
hint somewhere somewhere just say:
где-то намекнуть где-то просто сказать:
"Didn't you come to the sausage shop just in
"Тебе ли не пришла колбасный цех ты на
case figure out if it is well
всякий случай разбери хорошо ли оно у
collected at your place or some to that you can't
тебя собрано иди некоторые к тому нельзя
hint" he  will disassemble and assemble the
намекнуть" он разберёт и соберёт
modern era who bought the line assembled
современную эпоху кто купил линию собрал
he will say or something and there Sopudov will hold back the
он скажет что ли а там сопудов придержит
offer of this sausage that the population
предложение этой колбасы что население
support for the authorities in ninety-one that
поддержку власти в девяносто первом что
we saw no one came out to support the
мы видели никто не вышел поддерживать
authorities that for 6 years
власть которая за течение 6 лет
limited the supply of demand roughly
ограничивали предложение спроса грубо
speaking and here all this was leaked well this was leaked the
говоря и вот это всё слили ну это слили
fact is your Nazhdi and our driving
факт это ваши нажди и наши вождения
process happened we got unhooked but we
процесс произошёл мы отцепились но мы
were friendly but what does Yeltsin and your
были дружны но причём тут Ельцин и ваши
authorities have to do with it in the fourteenth year when you
власти в четырнадцатом году когда вы на
went to Gelyaka and said our people this
Геляку вышли и сказали наших людей эту
pride was brought to themselves and showed
гордость себе занесли и показывали до
until now this savagery are proud of how
сих пор вот этой дикости гордитесь как
you people with a crowbar
вы людей
you hear me so look yes
ломом вы меня слышите так смотри да
now I hear therefore look firstly
теперь слышу значит смотрите во-первых
while the Ukrainian leaders were Brezhnev
пока украинские вожди были Брежнев
Khrushchev the union was yes in Czechoslovakia in tanks
Хрущёв союз был да в Чехословаю в танки
they led to Vengyu everyone was afraid of us but as
водили в Венгю все боялись нас да как
soon as Gorbachev came immediately let's
только Горбачёв пришёл сразу давайте
liberalize yes your Gorbachev about with
либерализация да ваш Горбачёв про с
Yeltsin do not make excuses now
Ельциным не отмазывайтесь теперь
the fourteenth  year - this is a consequence of the
четырнадцатый год - это следствие
defeat of the Soviet Union in
поражения Советского Союза в девяносто
1991 that the union was given to the Americans the Americans have
первом году что союз отдали американцам
owned it since 1991 we have had no elections
владели у нас не было никаких выборов
it's all a farce the Americans put in the
это всё фарс американцы ставили тех
presidents and the deputies they
президентов и тех депутатов которые они
wanted yes do you believe in fair elections in
хотели да вы верите в честные выборы на
Ukraine the Americans became that's why
Украине американцы стали поэтому
1914 the Americans also
четырнадцатый год американцы также
made a Maidan the Americans brought in
сделали майдан американцы привели
Yanukovych the Americans overthrew us we can't
Януковича американцы скинули мы не можем
you betrayed us in 1991 handed us over to the
вы нас в девяносто первом году предали
Americans and that's
сдали америкам да и
all and you understand instead of
всё и всё понимаете вместо того чтобы
helping the Slavic brothers to free themselves from the
помочь братьям славянам освободиться от
Anglo-Saxon yoke yes nutcrackers
англо-саксонского ига да нуть орешников
in London in Washington and that's all and they would have
по Лондонуть по Вашингтону да и всё и
lived happily ever after 15 Slavic
жили б дружно счастливо 15 славянских
republics and so you understand well
республик а так что понимаешь ну
agree what Russia has done wait
согласись какие сделала Россия подожди
mouth listen to me what
рот слушай меня какие сделала Россия
steps Russia has taken to hit the Anglo-Saxons to
шаги чтобынуть по англосаксам чтобы
scare them to say: "Don't you dare
напугать их чтобы сказать: "Не смейте
touch Ukraine no need let them go
трогать Украину не надо отпустите их
let them live normally like they
пусть они живут нормально как в
lived in the Soviet Union" but you no you just went
Советском Союзе жили" а вы нет вы взяли
and started  Moreover, the Anglo-Saxons tell
и начали больше того англосакцы говорят
us that Moscow is the enemy, people say: "No,
нам что враг Москва люди говорят: "Нет
Moscow is a friend, we lived as Slavs, Rus' was there and that was it, the
Москва друг мы жили славяне Русь там и
Union," but now when
всё да Союз" вот а теперь когда ракеты
Russian missiles are flying into Ukraine, people are like:
российские летят в Украину люди такие:
"But what about Moscow, our friend, if Moscow is
"А как же Москва друг если Москва нас
bombing us?"  Mr. Popi again for a long time I will get
бомбит?" Пан Попи опять долго я
confused a lot of questions throw
запутаюсь много вопросов кидайте
false ones let me continue answering or
ложных давайте я продолжу отвечать или
will you conduct a monologue look
вы будете монолога вести смотрите
carefully well you we are a historical perspective
внимательно ну вы мы исторический ракурс
I was conducting until ninety-one but then
я вёл до девяносто первого года но потом
also a series of events were you
тоже череда событий были вы прекрасно
separated perfectly 30 years lived existed
отделились 30 лет жили существовали
notice 20 years lived got rich
замечаете 20 лет жили убогатели
sold all these and to you no one with not
распродавали все эти и вам никто с не
Americans look everything is good good
американцы смотри все хорошо хорошо
only specifically on the last you did not
только конкретно на последнее вы не
interrupt I will be brief not historical
перебивали я буду кратко не исторически
course I stop well you are offering to
курс прекращаю ну вы предлагаете себя
sell yourself to someone again but are you really
опять продать кому-то но вы ужели
selling completely there is nothing we can not
полностью продавать нечего мы не можем
sell in ninety-one Gorbachev
продать в девяносто первом году Горбачёв
and Yeltsin sold Ukraine to Bush Jr.
и Ельцин продали Украину Бушу младшему
George Bush Jr. president and
Джорджу Бушу младшему президенту и
Reagan yes everything and everything you understand everything we do
Рейгану да всё и всё понимаешь всё мы с
not own since ninety-one they
девяносто первого года не владеем нам
made us in ninety-sixth year the
сделали в девяносто шестом году
Anglo-Saxons constitution wrote in there
англосакци конституцию вписали туда
all their pseudo-democratic
всякие свои псевдодемократические
values ​​and everything you are responsible for everything since
ценности и всё вы ответственны за всё с
ninety-one you gave  us
девяносто первого года вы отдали нас
Slavic brothers on the Potala Anglo-Saxon you
славян братьев на поталу англосаксом вы
and do not need to throw off responsibility from yourself
и не надо с себя скидывать
where are the tanks on Berlin where is the
ответственность где танки на Берлин где
restoration of control over the Reichstag where is the
восстановление контроля над Рейкстагом
Berlin Wall where is the threat to the English Channel where are the
где берлинская стена где угроза Ламаншу
tank wedges on the English Channel yes where is the
где танковые клиния на Ламанш да где
air control of American
контроль воздушный американских
planes in the Pacific Ocean why not the
самолётов в Тихом океане почему нет
Americans fly in the Black Sea as if at
американцы в Чёрном море летают как у
home as if over Perth Harbor yes over the
себя дома будто над Перт Харбором да над
Slavic Crimea American
славянским Крымом летают американские
intelligence officers fly and you can not do anything so turn on the
разведчики и вы ничего не можете сделать
sound so therefore
вот так включайте звук поэтому поэтому
everything will be great wonderful nation of Ukraine
всё будет здорово замечательная нацию
I for you I turned on the sound for you can
укра я тебе я тебе включил звук можешь
repeat again what you turned on now
повторить заново что включил теперь
turned on repeat again
включил повтори заново
look wonderful Ukrainian
смотрите замечательная украинская
culture the nation existed and
культура нация существовала и существует
still exists but it is deprived of rights by the
до сих пор но она поражена в правах
Nazi here is the layer of society
нацистской вот прослойкой общества
which has affected its consciousness for the last 10 years
которое поразило её последние 10 лет
and absolutely many like the Nazis
сознание и абсолютно многие как нацисты
in Germany did not yet know that they were Nazis
в Германии ещё не знали что они нацисты
in April forty-fifth then having watched the
в апреле сорок пятого потом посмотрев
video they were very surprised and hence
видео они много удивились а отсюда
now the position is such unfortunately our
сейчас позиция такая к сожалению наши
existing state diverged in
государство существующее разошлись в
polar vision like Poland and Russia, let's
полярном видении как Польша и Россия
say, to us in the 15th century  understand that the war
допустим нам в XV веке поймите что война
divided us we are not brothers we are brothers but
нас разделила мы не братья мы братья но
brothers often fight yes even worse than
братья часто воюют да даже хуже чем
neighbors live and here is our position now
соседи живут и вот позиция наша сейчас
if in your society healthy people
такая если вашем обществе здоровые люди
vote for Russia we will happily
проголосуют за Россию мы счастливо
accept them our embrace if not yes thank
примем их наши объятия если нет да слава
God live in the positions in which you live
богу живите в тех позиции каких живёте
you were obliged to pass this for the
вы это обязаны были пройти за
tests that you ate up the Russian world that
тестки то что вы проедали русский мир то
you were proud for this savagery for this
вы гордились за эту дикость за это
barbarity for May 2 everything you are for the fact that you will
варваство за 2 мая всё вы за то что вы
win and now I mister pan
победите и сейчас я вас господин пан
Popik did not understand your position at all here is
Попик от слова совсем не понял вашу
your turn it's a pity that I did not
позицию вот ваш разворот жалко что я не
record your videos hello to subscribers
записывал ваши видео привет подписчикам
Russia is with
россия с
you so here is the question you say that we
вами так вот вопрос вы говорите что
will vote like the Americans will let us
проголосуем как американцы дадут нам
vote the central voter the
проголосовать центральный избиратель
Central Electoral Commission in
Центральная избирательная комиссия в
these and is led by the Anglo-Saxons everything they will
этих и руководится англосаксами всё они
draw any numbers you want there
нарисуют любые цифры какие хочешь там
is a pi nodding he will write everything yes as the
есть пи кивала он всё напишет да как
Anglo-Saxons do they will not give us at least
делают англосаксы они не дадут нам хоть
100 people at least 100% will vote for
100 человек хоть 100% проголосуют за
Russia they will write  01% and that's all that's the
Россию они напишут 01% и всё вот в чём
problem until you are in the Anglo-Saxon den,
проблема пока вы не у кубло англосаксов
this is Washington and MI6 in London, nothing will happen,
это Вашингтон и Ми-6 в Лондоне да ничего
nothing, that's why I say it again, yes,
не будет ничего поэтому я ещё раз говорю
until the Russian brothers, our Slavs, are
да пока русские братья наши славяне да
not a London solver, according to the Queen, you
не решником по Лондону по королеве вы же
know, the Queen is the King, they rule
знаете королева король они они правят
there, this Anglo-Saxon law,
там вот это англосаксонское право
British law, yes, they hold these Morgans,
британское да они держат эти морганы
Rotwells, they took everything into their own hands, and
ротвели они всё взяли в свои руки да и
we don't have anything that I, a simple person, can
мы ничего что я простой человек могу
do, that you can do,
сделать что вы можете сделать
even be a nutcracker according to Buckingham
даже быть у орешником по букингемскому
[laughter]
[смех]
How they float, yes, from the question: "Why did
Как они плывут да от вопроса: "Почему же
you attack your Slavic brothers and not the
вы напали на братьев славян а не на
Anglo-Saxons?"  Write in the comments a
англосакса?" Напишите в комментариях
good conversation strategy or not like
хорошая стратегия разговора или нет лайк
subscribe comment subscribe to th Telegram
подписка комент підпишись на й Telegram
right now axis vn and
прям зараз ось вн а
popik tse even more and more importantly youtube is
попик це дуже и дуже важливо youtube
banning us through kargeor into a shadow ban
заганяє нас через каргеор в тіньовий бан
and even a lot of the video is not shown to people
и дуже багато відео не показуется людям
often does not show information about streams
вчасно не показуец інформація про стрими
for this purpose.  operational connection
для того щоб ми мали оперативный зв'язок
subscribe directly immediately and the pop there in
підпишиться прямо зараз а попик там в
telegram okmdeo is also tsikava and useful
телеграмі окмдео ще теж цікава и корисна
information and we are loyal to the line of constant
інформація и мы повин трима постійний
operational connections
оперативний зв'язок
Regardless of that, I will show you about this
Незалежно від того чи покаже вам про цей
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube слава Україні підпишись